uti.edu 2012-11-30

# Universal Technical Institute Privacy Policy | UTI.edu

Universal Technical Institute (UTI) includes Custom Training Group, NASCAR Technical Institute, Motorcycle Mechanics Institute and Marine Mechanics Institute, which are subsidiaries of Universal Technical Institute,Inc. 

**Postal Address** :   
16220 N. Scottsdale Rd., Suite 100  
Scottsdale, AZ 85254

### Privacy

UTI is committed to protecting the privacy of our customer's personal information. This Policy explains how we gather and use the information that we collect from the [uticorp.com](http://www.uticorp.com/), uti.edu, [mmitech.edu](http://www.mmitech.edu/) and [mmi-marine.com](http://www.mmi-marine.com/) web sites. This policy may change over time and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof. 

UTI does not sell or rent any personal data you have provided to us to any third parties. We respect the privacy of users visiting our sites. We may use certain directory information that we have collected to send you information about our products and services, or updates and other information that we think may be of interest to you; and we may share this information with our educational subsidiaries to bring similar information to your attention. 

Other than directory information, data you provide to us as you use our Web site will be held in confidence by us and will be used for internal purposes only. We may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. However, the individual information you provide us within the Universal Technical Institute Web site will be known only to you and Universal Technical Institute. We will not share your personal data with anyone else, except as may be required by law. 

UTI uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy)."

###  Cookies

Cookies refer to data created by a Web server that is stored on a user’s computer. It provides a way for the Web site to keep track of a user’s patterns and preferences and, with the cooperation of the Web browser, to store them on the user’s own hard disk. 

The cookies contain a range of URLs (Web addresses) for which they are valid. When the browser encounters those URLs again, it sends those specific cookies to the Web server. For example, if a user’s ID were stored as a cookie, it would save that person from typing in the same information all over again when accessing that service for the second and subsequent time during the same browser session. 

We currently do not set any cookies. Our Web server does not automatically recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail addresses of visitors to our Web sites. We only collect information that you provide us when you request information by filling out our online “request” form, such as (your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, education background, etc.). 

###  How Do We Use Info Collected?

We use the information you provide to improve the design and content of our Web site for the benefit of the users of our Web site. In addition, the information you provide us is used for marketing purposes, and may result in follow-up communications via mail, e-mail or telephone. If you do not wish to receive such contact, please let us know by writing to us at the e-mail address or by calling us at the telephone number provided below, and providing us with your name, address and phone number. We will remove/deactivate your contact information from our database.   

### Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, Universal Technical Institute, Inc has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to secure the information we collect online. This Web site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information.

### Links To Other Web Sites

This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Universal Technical Institute, Inc is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. If you want to know the privacy policies of the other Web sites, please refer to the organization sponsoring such Web site.

### Email Unsubscribe Link

You may opt-out of receiving e-mail communications from Universal Technical Institute, Inc at the following link - [Unsubscribe Link](mailto:unsubscribe@uticorp.com).

### Contact Universal Technical Institute, Inc.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at [privacy@uticorp.com](mailto:privacy@uticorp.com) or by telephone at 623-445-9500.
